Charles Wharton Stork Papers
Charles Wharton Stork Papers
- Writings (1993 accession)
  - Harvard College Class of 1903, photocopied flyer (not in folder) (Box 5)
  - Semele, A Dramatic Idyll in Two Scenes, typescript play in binder (Box 5)
  - Aunt Elsbettel (Box 5)
  - Aunt Elsbettel (Box 5)
  - Merribel's Afternoon: A Flower Fantasy in One Act, typescript play (Box 5)
  - The Idiot, A Drama in Two Parts: Adapted from the Novel by Fydor Dostoyevsky, typescript play (Box 5)
  - Aunt Elsbettel, typescript play (Box 5)
  - Lisl's – Children's Book, only 76 Pages (Box 5)
  - Mustard Magill, typescript and holograph manuscript in box (Box 5)
  - Sharing: A Christmas Romance-New Style, typescript/manuscript in binder (Box 5)
  - Sharing, in envelope (Box 5)
  - Sharing – in folder (Box 5)
  - Susie's Folks, typescript play in binder (Box 5)
  - Mustard Magill, typescript/manuscript in envelope "Baseball Novel" (Box 5)
  - Getting Together, Novel carbon typescript/manuscript in envelope (Box 5)
  - The Stars Above, typescript play in envelope (Box 5)
  - Misc. play fragments, typescript in envelope (Box 5)
  - Out of the Dark, typescript and holograph play (Box 5)
  - The Flowers Come Alive, typescript play in envelope (Box 5)
  - Watt (Whitman): The Pageant of an American, holograph play in envelope (Box 5)
  - La Donna Velata, typescript manuscript collection of poetry in binder (Box 5)
  - Out of the Dark, typescript play in envelope (Box 5)
  - Poetry by CWS (Box 6)
  - Poetry by CWS (Box 6)
  - The Prayer of the Body, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - The Mystic at the Mast Head, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Excursion with a Trunk, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Perjury, typescript play (Box 6)
  - A Live wire, typescript story (Box 6)
  - Ninon 1, typescript play (Box 6)
  - Ninon II, typescript play (Box 6)
  - Ninon III, typescript play (Box 6)
  - Ninon IV, typescript play (Box 6)
  - Ninon V, typescript play (Box 6)
  - Ninon VI, typescript play (Box 6)
  - Ninon, typescript play (Box 6)
  - Ninon, carbon copy (Box 6)
  - Misc. Poetry (Box 6)
  - Keppler's Nude, typescript story (Box 6)
  - For a Time of Trial, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Winter Afterglow, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Second Sight by Per Hallström, translation by CWS holograph essay (Box 6)
  - Poetry by Hugo Von Hofmannsthal, translation by CWS typescript poems (Box 6)
  - Before Day by Hugo Von Hofmannsthal, translation by CWS typescript poem (Box 6)
  - The Youth and the Spider by Hugo Von Hofmannsthal, translation by CWS – typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems (Box 6)
  - For a National Poetry Day, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - The Meeting of Christ and Pan, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - The Triumph of Love, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - At the Grave of Perrault, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - As an Affirmation for Walt Whitman, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - A Wissahickon Walk, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - The Wren's Nest, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - The Gossips, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - The Mystic in the Grand Stand, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Have Faith, America, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - A Seaside Lake in Summer, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Autumn Acclamation, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Fellowship Restored, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - A Suite for Kwan-Yin, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Elaine Psychoanalyzes, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Acapulco, Mexico, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Cloud Intimations, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Benares, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Hong Kong, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Ode to Sanity, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - From Gottenburg to Stockholm: A Trip on the Gota Canal, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - 1 Will Dance, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - A Boy's Memory of a Stranger, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, typescript poems (Box 6)
  - To Stones from a New England Beach, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Athens, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Tribute to John Masefield from America, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Reverberations, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - The Discarded Christmas Tree, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, typescript poems (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, holograph poems (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems (Box 6)
  - Earth is a Recollection and a Promise, holograph poem – 2 copies (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, typescript poems (Box 6)
  - Misc. writings, typescript – Danish Poetry (Box 6)
  - Whitman and Wagner: A Comparison and Contrast, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Music Memories of an Amateur, typescript letter (Box 6)
  - The Burning City by Hjalman Södenberg, translation by CWS typescript story (Box 6)
  - Celia Martindale, holograph story (Box 6)
  - Too Bad About Percy, typescript and holograph story (Box 6)
  - Unidentified play fragments, typescript (Box 6)
  - Swedish Literature, holograph essay (Box 6)
  - Trial by Sonnets, holograph story (Box 6)
  - Whitman and Wagner: A Comparison and Contrast, holograph essay (Box 6)
  - The Educated American: From the Angle of a Writer, holograph essay (Box 6)
  - Ode to American Pointers, holograph poem (Box 6)
  - To Him that Hath, holograph poem (Box 6)
  - Biography and the Human Heart, review by CWS typescript (Box 6)
  - Northland Music, typescript story Shira; typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Escapism, holograph essay (Box 6)
  - Far-Borne Echoes, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Twice Facing Death, holograph story (Box 6)
  - The Forgotten Word, holograph essay (Box 6)
  - A Defense of Recent American Poetry, holograph essay (Box 6)
  - The Sons and Daughters of the Vikings, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Walt Whitman Today, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - A Hell of a Critic, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Swedish Literature, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - A Hell of a Critic, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Erik Axel Karlfeldt, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Castle Unrest by E.A. Karlfeldt, translated by CWS holograph poem (Box 6)
  - Bandits by the Bay of Naples, typescript story (Box 6)
  - Archimedes' Point by Hjalman Södenberg, translation by CWS typescript story (Box 6)
  - The Poetry of Weiharen, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Letter from Miss Patricia Chapness to CWS, typescript (Box 6)
  - Unidentified play fragment, typescript (Box 6)
  - Vermland poems, typescript and manuscript poems and essays (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, holograph poems (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, holograph poems (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, holograph poems (Box 6)
  - Misc. writings, holograph (Box 6)
  - The Ball: A Heroic poem, holograph poem (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, holograph poems (Box 6)
  - A Poor Monk of Skara, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Gallery Proof of Fröding's poems (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, holograph poems (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, translated by CWS typescript (Box 6)
  - Song of the Figurehead by Kai Friis Moller, translation by CWS typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Summer Dreams at Sea by Holger Drachman, translation by CWS typescript – poem (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, translated by CWS (Box 6)
  - Karin by Gustaf Geijerstom, translation by CWS typescript story (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, translated by CWS (Box 6)
  - The Northland by Valdemar Rördam, translation by CWS holograph poem (Box 6)
  - Song After Harvest, holograph poem (Box 6)
  - Oh, Never Ask!, holograph poem (Box 6)
  - The White Dragons, holograph poem (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, holograph (Box 6)
  - Misc. poems, translated by CWS typescript (Box 6)
  - Misc. Reviews by CWS (Box 6)
  - Creative Unity, review by CWS typescript (Box 6)
  - Thomas Hastings: Architect and Prophet, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Verse at Opposite Poles, review by CWS typescript (Box 6)
  - Six Volumes of Verse, review by CWS typescript and holograph (Box 6)
  - An Englishman for an Hour, holograph essay (Box 6)
  - The Magic Flute, review by CWS holograph (Box 6)
  - Three Studies in Shelley and an essay (Box 6)
  - an Nature in Words Worth and Meredith, review by CWS typescript (Box 6)
  - Mr. Bennett Near his Best, review by CWS typescript (Box 6)
  - The Gottenburg Exposition, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Five Poetry Books by Men, review by CWS typescript (Box 6)
  - Untitled Article (Box 6)
  - Part Truth Dispensed by Mr. Orrick Johns, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - A 'New' Definition of Poetry, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Art for Life's Sake, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - An Artist's Paradise, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - A Review of Magazine Verse in the United States, review by CWS typescript (Box 6)
  - American Magazine Verse for 1917, typescript essay (Box 6)
  - Misc. Poetry, typescript (Box 6)
  - The Parade, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Riding Song, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Ballade of American Poets 1917, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Realities of War, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - The Other Cheek, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Two Types of Heroes, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Hymn in War Time, typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Charleston, S.C., typescript poem (Box 6)
  - Box Containing plays "Sharing" and "Getting Together" (Box 6)
  - The Faith of Tristan (Box 6)
  - The Stars Above (Box 6)
  - Getting Together, play in binder (Box 7)
  - Sharing, holograph play in envelope (Box 7)
  - The Deathless Don, typescript play in envelope (Box 7)
  - The Flowers Come Alive, typescript play in envelope (Box 7)
  - Misc. writings (Box 7)
  - Walt: The Pageant of an American, typescript play in envelope (Box 7)
  - Flower Inferno by Ernst F. Löhndorff, translation by CWS typescript/manuscript in binder (Box 7)
  - The Ineffable Name: A Fantasy of the Word War by Waldemar Ager, translation by CWS typescript/manuscript (Box 7)
  - Misc. plays, typescript (Box 7)
  - Misc. plays (Box 7)
  - Misc. writings (Box 7)
  - Misc. writings (Box 7)
  - Misc. writings (Box 7)
  - Misc. writings (Box 7)
  - Misc. writings (Box 7)
  - Why Do We Travel?, typescript essay (Box 7)
  - The Unattained Meredith, typescript essay (Box 7)
  - Misc. Correspondences to CWS (Box 7)
  - Misc. Correspondences to CWS (Box 7)
  - Misc. Correspondences to CWS (Box 7)
  - Misc. writings, holograph (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems, typescript (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems, typescript and holograph (Box 8)
  - An Allegory (Box 8)
  - Rain, holograph poem (Box 8)
  - Winter Sunset: A Prose poem, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - The Queen of Orplede: A Romance, holograph play (Box 8)
  - Poetry vs. the Circumstances of writing, typescript essay (Box 8)
  - Unidentified play fragment (Box 8)
  - Falstaff an Broadway, typescript play in binder (Box 8)
  - The Prize Package, typescript play (Box 8)
  - Murder at Cambridge, typescript play (Box 8)
  - A Daughter of Boston 1, typescript story (Box 8)
  - A Daughter of Boston II, typescript story (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings, holograph (Box 8)
  - The Magnate, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - The Other Cheek, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - The Death of Hyacinth, holograph poem (Box 8)
  - The Concord of Learning, holograph poem (Box 8)
  - To a Suicide Poet, holograph poem (Box 8)
  - The Convict, holograph poem (Box 8)
  - Hyacinth O'Hara's Profession, holograph story (Box 8)
  - The New Nobel Prize Winner, Vernon Von Heidenstam, holograph essay (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings (Box 8)
  - A Dancer in a Cage, typescript story (Box 8)
  - 'The Open Secret" – Chapter III, typescript essay (Box 8)
  - Needed, typescript story (Box 8)
  - How Father God was Snowbound by Rosa Fitinghoff, translation by CWS – typescript story (Box 8)
  - Horne, typescript essay (Box 8)
  - The Nails, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems (Box 8)
  - The Marriage of Burns and Blake, typescript essay (Box 8)
  - A Brook in the Woods, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - Cairo, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - Athens, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - London, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - Buying a Present in Brittany, typescript story (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems (Box 8)
  - School Report and poem by Rosalie Stork (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings, mostly holograph (Box 8)
  - The Virile Dude (Fragment), typescript story (Box 8)
  - Celia Martindale, typescript story (Box 8)
  - Celia Martindale, typescript story (Box 8)
  - Faithless Tiliie Gursen, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - The Idiot, typescript play (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 8)
  - Sidney Lanier, A Poet We are Catching Up to, typescript essay (Box 8)
  - Self-Portrait, typescript essay (Box 8)
  - Both Sides of the Curtain, typescript essay (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings in notebook, holograph (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems (Box 8)
  - Hoffmansthal's Lyrics, review (Box 8)
  - The Yankee, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - Can I Let it Go On?, typescript story (Box 8)
  - Don Juan De Placensia, typescript play (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings (Box 8)
  - Fragment, typescript story(?) (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems (Box 8)
  - En Flamländsk Madonna, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - In Praise of Rhyme, typescript poem (Box 8)
  - Person Habits, typescript essay (Box 8)
  - Saving Selma, typescript story (Box 8)
  - The Natural Thing, typescript story (Box 8)
  - The Princess Brier-Rose by Sigfrid Lindstrom, translation by CWS typescript – story (Box 8)
  - The Puritan Confessor, typescript story (Box 8)
  - Northland Magic, typescript story (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings in notebook, holograph (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings, holograph (Box 8)
  - Misc. poems, holograph (Box 8)
  - Unidentified play fragment (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings (Box 8)
  - Misc. Swedish and Danish poems (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 8)
  - Being Estelle, typescript story (Box 8)
  - Perfect Transmission, typescript story (Box 8)
  - A Whiff of Tobacco, typescript story (Box 8)
  - A blicket Intrigue, holograph story (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 8)
  - Misc. writings (Box 8)
  - Clayton's Kick, typescript story (Box 8)
  - Misc. Children's poems by Elizabeth P. Stork? (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Letter of Acceptance to Mrs. Stork, manuscript (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems by Elizabeth Stork (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings in binder (Box 9)
  - Tatzlwurm im Heutal by Schulrat Josef Brettenthaler, summary by CWS (Box 9)
  - Vistas by Elizabeth Stork (Box 9)
  - The Intimate Stranger by LeRoy Smith Jr., published flyer (Box 9)
  - Misc. Correspondences and writings (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings by Elizabeth Stork (Box 9)
  - Jane Pratt: Counsellor at Love, holograph and typescript story (Box 9)
  - A Fishy Ghost, typescript story (Box 9)
  - With Sabres, typescript story (Box 9)
  - Ballad of Octogenarians, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - A Wissahickon Walk, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - The Great Regret, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Ode for the Tercentenary of Harvard College, 1936, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Rachmaninoff, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - The Yankee, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Man-Brutes, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Faithless Tillie Green, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - To Stone from a New England Beach, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Lighthouse Ledge, holograph manuscript in notebook (Box 9)
  - London, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - At the Grave of Perrault, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Lines for the Season of Poets, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Beside the Lake of Galilee, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Fanny Browne Reviews Her Memories, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Falterings Toward the Unknown God, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings in notebook, holograph (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings, holograph (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems, holograph (Box 9)
  - Unidentified play fragment (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings (Box 9)
  - To Kipling, Poet of Men, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems, typescript (Box 9)
  - A Boy's Memory of a Stranger, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - The Master's Bid Farewell, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Ballad of Octogenarians, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Daft Andy, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Man-Brutes, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings in notebook, holograph (Box 9)
  - For a Time of Trial, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - To George Meredith, typescript poem and clipping (Box 9)
  - Our Heritage, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems, typescript (Box 9)
  - American Bards Through British Eyes, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - To Kipling, Poet of Men, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - A Boy's Memory of a Stranger, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Apologia, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Earth is a Recollection and a Promise, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Shira, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Beside the Lake of Galilee, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Breaking (?) Shell, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Seeking a Personal God, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Poetry CWS, Martha's Vineyard (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - The Something Else, typescript story (Box 9)
  - Tagore's International College, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - Meeting in Hong Kong, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - The Stars Above, typescript play (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 9)
  - American Painting: Some Adventures in Appreciation, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - On the Reading of History, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - The Magic of Foreign Words: A Retrospect, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - Whitman and Wagner: A Comparison and Contrast, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - At Our Peril, typescript story (Box 9)
  - The Marriage of Burns and Blake, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - Toward the Inner Technic of Poetry, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - The Educated American: From the Angle of a Writer, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - Bandits by the Bay of Naples, typescript story (Box 9)
  - Nature in German Music, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems, typescript (Box 9)
  - Adventures in the Art of Teaching, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - Mustard Magill, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Ode to Scandinavia, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Edvard Grieg, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Ode to Sanity, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - For My Sister, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - A Straight Question, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - The Smile of Unity, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Apologia, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Whitsunday Morning at Leksand, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - A Land of Hospitality, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - Keene Valley and Lake Placid, typescript essay (Box 9)
  - Chant for Autumn, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - A Treasure Box, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Sketches by and 'Athenian', typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - The Taking of the Trireme, typescript poem (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Poems by Henrik Isben, translated by CWS (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Unidentified poem fragment, holograph (Box 9)
  - Misc. poems (Box 9)
  - Misc. writings (Box 10)
  - Misc. poems (Box 10)
  - Misc. poems (Box 10)
  - Misc. poems in envelope (Box 10)
  - Misc. poems in envelope (Box 10)
  - Misc. poems in envelope (Box 10)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 10)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 10)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 10)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 10)
  - Will's Reformation, typescript play (Box 10)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 10)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 10)
  - The Egoist, typescript play in binder (Box 10)
  - Ninon CWS, (carbon typescript) (Box 10)
  - Fragment in envelope, typescript prose (Box 10)
  - The Loyal Traitor, typescript story in envelope (Box 10)
  - Misc. writings and fragments in envelope (Box 10)
  - Susie's Folks, typescript play in envelope (Box 10)
  - Sparkling and Bright, musical score in envelope (Box 10)
  - Essays and Articles (Box 10)
  - Essays (Box 10)
  - Translations (Box 10)
  - Anthology – Contents (Box 10)
  - Misc. writings, holograph in notebook (Box 11)
  - Walt, play manuscript; typescript and holograph (Box 11)
  - Translations poems and plays at Penn (bound) (Box 11)
  - Play: Sick Child (Box 11)
  - Unidentified play, holograph and typescript (Box 11)
  - Poetry (Box 11)
  - Getting Together, holograph play (Box 11)
  - Danish translations by CWS (Box 11)
  - Norwegian translations by CWS (Box 11)
  - German translations by CWS (Box 11)
  - Swedish translations by CWS (Box 11)
  - Swedish translations by CWS (Box 11)
  - Manuscript of Hoffmansthal's Poetry, typescript (Box 11)
  - Nationalism in Swedish Poetry, holograph essay (Box 11)
  - The Poetry of Verner Von Heidenstam, typescript essay (Box 11)
  - Reviews of CWS's Anthology of Swedish Lyrics, typescript (Box 11)
  - The Poetry of Viktor Rydberg, typescript essay (Box 11)
  - Misc. poems, typescript (Box 11)
  - Riding Song, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Review of CWS's Anthology of Swedish Lyrics (Box 11)
  - Throw Wide the Window, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Swedish Poetry To-Day, typescript essay (Box 11)
  - Falterings Toward an Unknown God, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - For the Death of Woodrow Wilson, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - A Feast of Reason, reviewed by CWS typescript (Box 11)
  - Misc. poems (Box 11)
  - Sesqui-Centennial Ode, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Mr. Noyes and the Bacchus of Emerson, typescript essay (Box 11)
  - Review of CWS's Anthology of Swedish Lyrics (Box 11)
  - Poems of Russian Cities, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - I am Aware of Cities, title page, contents, etc... (Box 11)
  - Poems of Cities, holograph (Box 11)
  - Munich, typescript and holograph poem (Box 11)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 11)
  - Prague, holograph poem (Box 11)
  - Constantinople, holograph poem (Box 11)
  - Paris, holograph poem (Box 11)
  - Cairo, typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Boston, typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Washington, typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Richmond, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Newport, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Vienna, holograph poem (Box 11)
  - Stockholm, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Charleston, S.C., typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Thacher School Reunion Song, typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Philadelphia, typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Naples, typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Rome, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - New York, typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Athens, typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 11)
  - Faithless Tillie Green, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - When the Spirit Shall Prevail by Gunnar Reiss-Anderson, translation by CWS – holograph poem (Box 11)
  - The Year After by Gunnar Reiss-Anderson, translation by CWS typescript; poem (Box 11)
  - Godhead by Bertil Malmberg, translation by CWS typescript poem (Box 11)
  - A Poet's Confession by Bertil Malmberg, translation by CWS typescript poem (Box 11)
  - The Fable of the Caterpillar, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 11)
  - Karin, typescript 'Opera' script (play?) (Box 11)
  - Translated poem and Book Review (Box 11)
  - To —, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Helsingfors, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Chicago, holograph poem (Box 11)
  - Prelude, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Berlin, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Misc. poems (Box 11)
  - Misc. poems (Box 11)
  - Misc. poems (Box 11)
  - Misc. poems (Box 11)
  - Misc. poems (Box 11)
  - A Henchman of Gustaf Vasq, holograph novel (?) manuscript (Box 11)
  - A Shark at Moonstone Beach, typescript story (Box 11)
  - The 'Gravellotte' Rhapsody, typescript essay (Box 11)
  - Giorgio Vanni, typescript story (Box 11)
  - The Fatal Friend, typescript story (Box 11)
  - A Shark at Moonstone Beach, typescript story (Box 11)
  - The Queen of Orplede, holograph preface, title p., dedication (Box 11)
  - Actaeon, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Princess Flora, typescript novel (Box 11)
  - Aunt Elsbettel, typescript novel (Box 11)
  - To Edwin Arlington Robinson, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Misc. Music (Box 11)
  - Poetry by S.M. Bird (Box 11)
  - Misc. poems (Box 11)